stackadapt.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | StackAdapt

#### StackAdapt Privacy Policy

###### Last Updated: December 23, 2019

##### Our Commitment

StackAdapt strongly believes that all information deserves protection. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our privacy practices for our website ( _"Website"_ ) as well as our privacy practices for our services ( _"Services"_ ). We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. So we encourage you to review these pages on a regular basis.

##### How we collect personal information

We collect personal information directly from you when you provide information directly to us automatically through your use of our Website and Services or from third parties who you provided information to, such as providers related to our Services. As used in this Privacy Policy, "personal information" is information that could be reasonably used to identify you personally.

Information about our data collection during the prior 12 months is further described below.

You can access, delete and control certain uses of your information as set forth in the _"Your Choices"_ section below.

  1. _Information we collect from you directly_

The information we collect from you directly may include:

    * Personal contact information, such as full name, telephone number, e-mail address, mailing address and location which we use to respond to your inquiries, provide you with requested products or services and send you information and marketing related to the services we provide you
    * Correspondence you send to us, such as information you provide us when you contact us (to inquire about our service, request a demo or make inquiries to our webmaster), provide feedback or make a complaint which we use to reply to your inquiries.
  2. _Information we collect from you automatically or from third parties_

We use "pixel tags" and/or "cookies" to collect information from you when you use our Website or Services or the websites or services of our third party partners. Pixel tags are small bits of code that provide a method of delivery information on a webpage which allows the operator of the page or a third party to collect the IP address of the users of the page. Cookies are small text files that are stored on the browser of a computer that uniquely identify the browser and provide information to the cookie sender. Many websites send cookies to the browsers that are visiting those sites, and many browsers are initially configured to accept cookies. Users can change the browser settings to refuse cookies or to alert them when a cookie has been placed on their browser. The user can check the browser for details in this regard.

At StackAdapt, in accordance with the privacy policies of the websites and advertising networks we work with, we collect personal information including online identifiers and internet activity information such as Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser information, recent search history, and activity on various websites in order to display effective advertisements. Based on the behaviour and preferences of the users, we seek to group them into certain categories and display the most relevant advertisements to the users in those categories. We strictly follow the privacy policy of the website or other platforms we interact with.

##### How we use the information

StackAdapt uses your personal information that we collect from you directly, automatically or from third parties to:

  * Administer, troubleshoot, enhance and manage our Services
  * Send processing communications, including updates on your subscription or account
  * Send promotional communications such as special offers or other promotions (if you have subscribed)
  * Manage your account
  * Analyze the accuracy and effectiveness of our Website and Services
  * Analyzing and understanding our customers and their needs
  * Meet obligations as required by applicable laws, i.e. fraud detection, enforcing our business terms and agreements
  * Tailor your experience while visiting our website
  * Responding to inquiries, complaints and other communications to StackAdapt
  * Display advertisements that we believe may be relevant to the user. In seeking to identify relevant advertisements, we use online identifiers and internet activity information to create and refine user segments, to develop and refine algorithms, and to understand better how users' interaction with a website might be of interest to advertisers.

Please note that all of the information we collect about you may be combined, including to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop rich online content and services across our Website and Services. This privacy policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to us. If we combine information we receive from those other sources with personal information we collect through the Website and Services, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any personal information received, unless we have disclosed otherwise

##### Data Security, Storage and Retention

We employ all reasonable industry standard measures to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or destruction of the information we collect and our levels of safeguards correspond to the level of sensitivity of the information. While we are committed to ensuring the security of the information, no protection measure can provide a 100% guarantee of security. Consequently, we do not warrant or guarantee the security of the information.

Your information is stored and / or processed or otherwise used by or on behalf of StackAdapt. We retain your information for as long as necessary or relevant for the listed purposes in this Privacy Policy, or as required by any applicable legal and retention obligations.

##### Sharing Data

We share personal information with advertisers, partners, vendors, service providers and other trusted third parties in the following ways:

  * We may share information with our service providers in order to deliver our products and Services to you.
  * We may share information with third parties that use our Services on the StackAdapt Platform. We have agreements with such third parties that include clauses that hold our partners to the same high level of privacy protection we apply to the data and to never use the data for any other purpose than what we have committed to.
  * We may share information with our business and promotional partners to send you information, by email, telephone or other means, about products and services you may like. Users may opt-out of receiving communications at any time. See the "Your Choices" section below.
  * Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we never disclose any personal information that directly identifies you unless we are required by law and we would only do so having verified the lawful authority of the request, such as to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us and to defend against legal claims. We may also voluntarily disclose personal information as allowed by law to prevent fraudulent activities.
  * We may share your personal information to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us] about our Website or Service users is among the assets transferred.

##### Sales of Information

We may sell your personal information to third parties, subject to your right to opt-out of those sales (See the _"Your Choices"_ and _"Residents of California"_ sections below).

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have sold the following categories of personal information:

  * Personal identifiers
  * Internet or other similar network activity
  * Inferences drawn from other personal information
  * Location data

##### Mobile Advertising ID

StackAdapt may use Advertising Identifiers for in-app ad targeting on mobile devices. Mobile operating systems including Apple's iOS and Google's Android provide an option of opting out of targeted in-app ads. To opt out, the user simply navigates to the operating system settings and follows the instructions. We act accordingly.

##### Third party links

Our Website may be linked from another website, or have links to other websites such as social media platforms. This Privacy Policy only relates to our collection and use of your information on our Website and Services. StackAdapt is not responsible for the privacy practices of other third party websites. We encourage you to read all privacy policies of websites you visit.

##### Your choices

_Cookies:_  Most browsers are set up to accept cookies; however, the "help" feature of the menu bar on most browsers will explain how you can stop accepting cookies and how to turn off existing cookies. If you decide not to accept cookies you may not have access to certain features that make your experience of the website more efficient and some of the features on the website may not function properly.

_Interest-Based Advertising:_ We work with third parties who collect information on our Website, Services and elsewhere through the use of cookies and similar methods in order to serve you with relevant advertisements on other services or to determine that you have seen advertisements on other services. This method of advertising is sometimes called "interest-based advertising."

To learn more about Interest-Based Advertising and your choices with respect to it, and to opt-out of advertising programs that track your activities across multiple websites to deliver personalized advertising content to you, please visit:

  * For Canada: [Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada Opt-Out Page](https://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising)
  * For Canada and U.S.: [NAI Opt-Out Page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
  * For Canada and U.S.: [Ad Choices Opt-Out Page](https://www.aboutads.info/choices)
  * For European Residents: [Your Online Choices | EDAA](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

Scroll to the bottom to opt-out on this website.

Please note that if you opt-out you may still receive online advertising from StackAdapt on other websites or applications; however, these advertisements will not be displayed to you based on your interests. We do not respond to or honor "do not track" (a/k/a DNT) signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.

_Access Request:_  You can make a request directly to the organization using our services, in which case we will assist as necessary. If you make a request to us, we will let you know what personal information StackAdapt has about you, what it is being used for, and with whom it has been shared. If you notice any inaccuracies or wish to update any part of your personal information, we will look into that as well.

StackAdapt will provide you with access to your personal information that is in our possession, subject to certain exceptions, including information that is referenced to another individual's personal information that we cannot sever, or information subject to solicitor-client privilege, or other legal restrictions that may prevent us from fulfilling your access request. See below for contact details.

_Residents of the E.U.:_  Under the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), residents of the E.U. also have the right to request of erasure of personal data, right to restrict processing, and in certain circumstances the right to data portability. See below for contact details.

_Residents of California and Other Specific Jurisdictions:_ If you reside in California or in a jurisdiction that provides similar rights, under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) or applicable law, you have specific rights regarding your personal information. This section describes the rights that you have under CCPA, or other state laws as applicable, and explains how to exercise those rights.

  * Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed or Sold. You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection, use, disclosure or sale of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see _"Exercising Access, and Deletion Rights"_ ), and subject to certain limitations that we describe below, we will disclose such information to you. You have the right to request any or all of the following:

    * The categories of personal information we collected about you.
    * The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected.
    * Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
    * The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
    * The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you
  * Right to Request Deletion. You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see _"Exercising Access, and Deletion Rights"_ ), we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records. However, we may retain personal information that has been de-identified or aggregated. Furthermore, we may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) in order to perform certain actions set forth under CCPA, such as detecting security incidents and protecting against illegal activity.

  * Exercising Access and Deletion Rights. To exercise the access and deletion rights described above, please submit a request to us by sending an email to [privacy@stackadapt.com](mailto:privacy@stackadapt.com)

Only you, or a person or business entity registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf (an "authorized agent"), may make the requests set forth above. If you use an authorized agent to make a request, you must provide the authorized agent written permission to do so, and we may require that you verify your identity directly with us. You may also make a request on behalf of your minor child.

The request should include your contact information and describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. In addition, you should provide sufficient information (including, but not limited to, cookie ID and IP address) that allows us to reasonably verify that you are the person about whom we collected the personal information or an authorized representative.

We will respond to consumer requests in a reasonably timely manner. If we require extra time to respond, we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.

In order to protect the security of your personal information, we will not honor a request if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. The method used to verify your identity will vary depending on the nature of the request. Generally speaking, verification will be performed by matching the identifying information provided by you to the personal information that we already have.

Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding our receipt of your request. We are not obligated to provide the information set forth above under _"Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed or Sold"_ more than twice in a 12-month period.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

  * Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights. You have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information at any time (the "right to opt-out"). We do not sell the personal information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age, unless we receive affirmative authorization (the "right to opt-in") from either the consumer who is at least 13 and less than 16 years of age, or the parent or guardian of a consumer less than 13 years of age.

To exercise the right to opt-out, you (or your authorized representative) may submit a request to us by sending an email to [privacy@stackadapt.com](mailto:privacy@stackadapt.com) or by clicking Opt-Out link at the bottom of this page.

If you use an authorized agent to exercise the right to opt-out, you must provide the authorized agent written permission to do so, and we may deny the request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that it has been authorized by you to act on your behalf.

Non-Discrimination. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights.

_Opt-out of receiving marketing emails:_  In the event you wish to unsubscribe from receiving promotional email communications from StackAdapt you may opt-out by:

  * Removing yourself by clicking "unsubscribe" at the bottom of an email we send you, or
  * Contact us at: [privacy@stackadapt.com](mailto:privacy@stackadapt.com)

If you opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us, we may still send you important administrative messages relating to our business relationship.

##### Consent to Transfer

StackAdapt is headquartered in Canada and has partners in other countries. Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of our Website and Services may be collected in your country and subsequently transferred to Canada, the United States or another country in accordance with applicable law. The privacy and data protection laws in another country may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using our Website and Services or providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your information.

##### Contact Us

To contact us with questions about this Privacy Policy or to make a request:

**Email:**  

**Mail:**  
StackAdapt Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
500 - 210 King St. East  
Toronto, ON, Canada   
M5A 1J7 

* * *
